var questionBank = [
    {
    question: "1. Which of the following object is the main entry point to all client-side JavaScript features and APIs?",
    choices: ["a) Position", "b) Window", "c) Standard", "d) Location"],
    answer: "b) Window"
},
    {
    question: "2. Which of the following can be used to call a JavaScript Code Snippet?",
    choices: ["a) Function/Method", "b) Preprocessor", "c) Triggering Event", "d) RMI"],
    answer: "a) Function/Method"
},

    {
    question: "3. Arrays in JavaScript are defined by which of the following statements?",
    choices: ["a) It is an ordered list of values", "b) It is an ordered list of objects", "c) It is an ordered list of string", "d) It is an ordered list of functions"],
    answer: "a) It is an ordered list of values"
},

    {
    question: "4. The statement a===b refers to _________",
    choices: [ "a) Both a and b are equal in value, type and reference address", "b) Both a and b are equal in value", "c) Both a and b are equal in value and type", "d) There is no such statement"],
    answer: "c) Both a and b are equal in value and type"
},

    {
    question: "5. Among the keywords below, which one is not a statement?",
    choices: ["a) debugger", "b) with", "c) if", "d) use strict"],
    answer: "d) use strict"
},
{
    question: "6. Why is event handlers needed in JS?",
    choices: ["a) Allows JavaScript code to alter the behaviour of windows", "b) Adds innerHTML page to the code", "c) Change the server location", "d) Performs handling of exceptions and occurrences"],
    answer: "a) Allows JavaScript code to alter the behaviour of windows"
},
    {
    question:"7. A function definition expression can be called as __________",
    choices: ["a) Function prototype", "b) Function literal", "c) Function calling", "d) Function declaration"],
    answer: "b) Function literal"
},

    {
    question: "8. Among the following, which one is a ternary operator?", 
    choices: ["a) +", "b) :", "c) â€“", "d) ?:"],
    answer: "d) ?:"
},

    {
    question: "9. A conditional expression is also called a _______________",
    choices: ["a) Alternative to if-else", "b) Immediate if", "c) If-then-else statement", "d) Switch statement"],
    answer: "b) Immediate if"
},

    {
    question: "10. Which of the operator is used to test if a particular property exists or not?",
    choices: ["a) in", "b) exist", "c) within", "d) exists"],
    answer: "a) in"
}
]




